Every physics student has done this:
memorize a formula, plug in numbers...
...and get an answer you don't actually understand.
Real labs are expensive — most of us never touch one.
So we built a physics lab that lives in your browser.
Axiom Studio — physics you can actually touch.
Any browser becomes a real physics lab.
No account, no setup — just open it.
Under the hood: real physics engines,
RK4 integration, true orbital mechanics.
Not fake animations — the real deal.
Here's what makes it different. Every experiment
follows three steps. First: predict.
Before anything runs, I commit to an answer.
Will this projectile land here, or here?
Then: experiment. Adjust the parameters —
angle, velocity — and run the real simulation.
And finally: understand.
Meet Axion, our AI tutor.
It doesn't give a generic textbook answer — it reads
your numbers and prediction, and explains exactly why.
Projectile motion is just the start.
Pendulum dynamics for harmonic motion.
Collision physics for conservation laws.
And my favorite — orbital mechanics, in full 3D.
Same loop every time: predict, experiment, understand.
That's how real intuition gets built — accessible
to anyone with a browser.
For free. Built for DHS Hacks — live now at
axiom-studio20.vercel.app.
Thanks for watching.